Finding Aid for the Joseph Chouinard Collection of Images, circa 1928-2006
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Smaller format photographs, circa 1928-circa 1981, III.; Item 070-200
  - Thomas and Joseph Chouinard with Joyce Flood standing in front of a rock on Cadillac Mountain, 1933 August 20, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Bar Harbor (Me.) On verso: "Tom, Joe & Joyce, top of Cadilac [sic] Mtn." Note: Joyce Flood was another of the foster or adopted children at the home of George and Elizabeth Bradley. (Box 1, Image 078)
  - Thomas and Joseph Chouinard with two unidentified girls (the one on the far right was identified as Joyce Flood on another photograph), 1933, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 079)
  - Thomas and Joseph Chouinard with fellow foster or adopted child, Joyce Flood, 1933, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 080)
  - Thomas and Joseph Chouinard with their adoptive mother, Elizabeth Bradley, 1933, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 081)
  - Joseph Chouinard standing in front of a house, 1933, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location Probably 215 Prospect Street, Middletown, Connecticut (Box 1, Image 082)
  - School portrait of Joseph Chouinard, circa 1935, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 083)
  - School portrait of Thomas Chouinard, circa 1935, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 084)
  - School portrait of Thomas Chouinard, circa 1936, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 085)
  - Joseph and Thomas Chouinard on the steps of a house, 1936 September, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 086)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Airplane view of P.P. highway, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 087)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Pike's Peak from Colo. Springs, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 088)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Pike's Peak from Mile 4, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 089)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Looking down from Mile 14, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 090)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: At timberline, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 091)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: The W's or switchbacks, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 092)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Glen Cove, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 093)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: The W's above Glen Cove, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 094)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: One of the many wide curves, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 095)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Above the clouds, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 096)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Pike's Peak from Pilot Knob, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 097)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Ute Pass, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 098)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Above Glen Cove, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 099)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: At timberline, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 100)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: 25% grade, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 101)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Lake Moraine, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 102)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Above the timberline, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 103)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: Pike's Peak summit house, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 104)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: The rocky summit, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 105)
  - 20 original photographs of the Pike's Peak trip: The observatory, 1937 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Stewart Brothers (Firm) Location: Pikes Peak (Colo.) (Box 1, Image 106)
  - Joseph and Thomas Chouinard, with Joyce Flood and an unidentified girl at a beach, 1938 August, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 107)
  - Thomas and Joseph Chouinard (right) in suit coats outside a house, 1939 November, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 108)
  - Joseph Chouinard with an unidentified male and female at the Holy Trinity Church in Middletown, Connecticut, 1939 December, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Middletown (Conn.) Venue: Church of the Holy Trinity (Middletown, Conn.) (Box 1, Image 109)
  - Joseph Chouinard with two unidentified males at Holy Trinity Church in Middletown, Connecticut, 1939 December, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Middletown (Conn.) Venue: Church of the Holy Trinity (Middletown, Conn.) On verso: Trinity Church, with organist (Box 1, Image 110)
  - Joseph Chouinard in his robe for graduation from 8th grade, 1940 August, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Middletown (Conn.) (Box 1, Image 111)
  - Identification photograph of Joseph Chouinard in his naval uniform, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 112)
  - Joseph Chouinard in his naval uniform with an unidentified young boy also in a uniform, 1945 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 113)
  - Joseph Chouinard in his naval uniform with an unidentified young boy also in a uniform, 1945 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 114)
  - Joseph Chouinard in his naval uniform with an unidentified young boy also in a uniform, 1945 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 115)
  - Joseph Chouinard in his naval uniform standing next to a house, 1945 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 116)
  - Joseph Chouinard in his naval uniform standing on a lawn, 1945 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 117)
  - Joseph Chouinard in his naval uniform on duty in Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown city in Okinawa On verso: A. L. Lawrence, … CUB 16, A-2 … (Box 1, Image 118)
  - Ruins of Shuri Boys' High School on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Shuri-shi (Japan) On verso: University of Naha. (Box 1, Image 119)
  - Torii gate in Naha on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Naha-shi (Japan) (Box 1, Image 120)
  - Okinawans sharing tea towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 121)
  - Woman washing her hair at a cistern on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 122)
  - Okinawan refugees near a building with a thatched roof on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 123)
  - Two Okinawan men working outside on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 124)
  - Okinawa women refugees gathered outside a food distribution center on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa Information courtesy of Mr. Donn Cuson, who also stated: "... note the pile of sweet potatoes, everything was on the barter system during that period, food for work. The US military government provided food and shelter and the Okinawans would go out and work the fields and the food would be divided among all of the people at the camps. " (Box 1, Image 125)
  - Okinawan refugees along a road on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 126)
  - Native police unit on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa Information supplied by Mr. Donn Cuson: "NP Native Police, trained and used by the US Military Government to watch and help in the refugee camps." (Box 1, Image 127)
  - Building on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 128)
  - Woman hanging clothes to dry on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 129)
  - Okinawan refugees walking on a dirt road on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 130)
  - Okinawan Children on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 131)
  - Okinawan child standing by herself on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 132)
  - Okinawan children along a dirt road on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 133)
  - Okinawan child standing on a dirt road on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 134)
  - Ornate table inside the Higaonna Museum in Ishikawa, Okinawa shortly after the museum's opening in September 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Ishikawa-shi (Japan) Information courtesy of Mr. Donn Cuson (Box 1, Image 135)
  - Exterior of the Higaonna Museum in Ishikawa, Okinawa shortly after the museum's opening in September 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Ishikawa-shi (Japan) Information courtesy of Mr. Donn Cuson (Box 1, Image 136)
  - Okinawan child standing next to a rock wall on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 137)
  - Okinawan woman with two children on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 138)
  - Okinawan woman with four children behind her on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 139)
  - Three Okinawan children on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 140)
  - Decorative table inside Higaonna Museum in Ishikawa, Okinawa shortly after its opening in September 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Ishikawa-shi (Japan) Information courtesy of Mr. Donn Cuson (Box 1, Image 141)
  - Exterior of the Higaonna Museum in Ishikawa, Okinawa shortly after its opening in September 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Ishikawa-shi (Japan) Information courtesy of Mr. Donn Cuson (Box 1, Image 142)
  - Shelf holding vases inside Higaonna Museum in Ishikawa, Okinawa shortly after its opening in September 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Ishikawa-shi (Japan) Information courtesy of Mr. Donn Cuson (Box 1, Image 143)
  - Buddhist shrine inside Higaonna Museum in Ishikawa, Okinawa shortly after its opening in September 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Ishikawa-shi (Japan) Information courtesy of Mr. Donn Cuson (Box 1, Image 144)
  - Small shrine inside Higaonna Museum in Ishikawa, Okinawa shortly after its opening in September 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Ishikawa-shi (Japan) Information courtesy of Mr. Donn Cuson (Box 1, Image 145)
  - Exterior of the Higaonna Museum in Ishikawa, Okinawa shortly after its opening in September 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Ishikawa-shi (Japan) Information courtesy of Mr. Donn Cuson (Box 1, Image 146)
  - Okinawan people aboard a horse-drawn wagon on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 147)
  - Two United States servicemen examining remains of a Japanese pilot and his plane on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa Information supplied by Mr. Donn Cuson: "During the war there was an attempted suicide attack by airplane at one of the airfields on Okinawa, several Japanese planes with troops tried to land and attack the airfield, this is one of the Japanese soldiers after the attack failed. " (Box 1, Image 148)
  - Remains of a building at a Naval Supply Depot on Okinawa the day that Typhoon Louise hit the island, 1945 October 9, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa Information supplied by Mr. Donn Cuson: "Navy Supply Depot, most likely the installation at Tengan. Major damage on Okinawa, 80% of military installations damage or destroyed. Over 200 ships and aircraft damaged or destroyed. 36 killed and 47 missing." (Box 1, Image 149)
  - United States Naval Supply Depot on Okinawa sometime after Typhoon Louise hit the island October 9 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa Information supplied by Mr. Donn Cuson: "Navy Supply Depot, most likely the installation at Tengan. Major damage on Okinawa, 80% of military installations damage or destroyed. Over 200 ships and aircraft damaged or destroyed. 36 killed and 47 missing." (Box 1, Image 150)
  - Remains of the railroad station at Naha, Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Naha-shi (Japan) On verso: What is left of the railroad station and trains at Naha. It was a narrow gauge rail line that ran from Naha south to Itoman and north to Kadena. Information courtesy of Mr. Donn Cuson. (Box 1, Image 151)
  - Unidentified serviceman in pith helmet on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 152)
  - Joseph Chouinard on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945 December 10, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 153)
  - Joseph Chouinard on Okinawa towards the end of World War II, 1945 December 10, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 154)
  - United States C-54 plane used to transport Japanese surrender delegation from the base on Iejima, an island off Okinawa, to Manila on August 19, 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Iejima (Japan) (Box 1, Image 155)
  - Japanese Mitsubishi G4M Betty bomber with special markings used to fly the Japanese surrender delegation to the base on Iejima, an island off Okinawa, August 19, 1945, 1945 August 19, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Iejima (Japan) (Box 1, Image 156)
  - Grave sites on Okinawa, including D. E. Smith, R. I. Dunn, and Simon Bolivar Buckner, Jr., 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa Simon Bolivar Buckner, Jr. (July 18, 1886-June 18, 1945), Lieutenant General, U.S. Army, killed by enemy fire at the Battle of Okinawa during World War II (Box 1, Image 157)
  - Dentist examining teeth of an Okinawan, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 158)
  - Japanese flight crew of one of the two Mitsubishi G4M Betty bombers that flew the Japanese surrender delegation to Iejima, an island off Okinawa, August 19, 1945, 1945 August 19, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location in Okinawa (Box 1, Image 159)
  - Members of the Japanese surrender delegation waiting to board the United States C-54 plane at the Iejima base before flying to Manila August 19, 1945, 1945, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Iejima (Japan) (Box 1, Image 160)
  - Lieutenant General Torasirou Kawabe (center), Vice Chief of the Japanese Army General Staff, and other members of the Japanese surrender delegation on the island of Iejima with United States military personnel before flying to Manila, August 19, 1945, 1945 August 19, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Iejima (Japan) (Box 1, Image 161)
  - Lieutenant General Torasirou Kawabe (center), Vice Chief of the Japanese Army General Staff, and other members of the Japanese surrender delegation on the island of Iejima before flying to Manila, August 19, 1945, 1945 August 19, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Iejima (Japan) (Box 1, Image 162)
  - Joseph Chouinard and adoptive mother Elizabeth Bradley in a cemetery, 1947 April, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 163)
  - Joseph Chouinard in cap and gown for graduation from University of Connecticut, 1950 June 11, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Storrs (Conn.) (Box 1, Image 164)
  - Joseph Chouinard in cap and gown for graduation from University of Connecticut, 1950 June 11, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Storrs (Conn.) (Box 1, Image 165)
  - Joseph Chouinard in cap and gown for graduation from University of Connecticut, 1950 June 11, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Storrs (Conn.) (Box 1, Image 166)
  - Joseph Chouinard in cap and gown for graduation from University of Connecticut, 1950 June 11, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Storrs (Conn.) (Box 1, Image 167)
  - Joseph Chouinard in cap and gown for graduation from University of Connecticut, 1950 June 11, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Storrs (Conn.) (Box 1, Image 168)
  - Joseph Chouinard in cap and gown for graduation from University of Connecticut, 1950 June 11, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Storrs (Conn.) (Box 1, Image 169)
  - Joseph Chouinard in cap and gown for graduation from University of Connecticut standing with unidentified woman and man, 1950 June 11, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Storrs (Conn.) (Box 1, Image 170)
  - Joseph Chouinard in suit and tie, 1951 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 171)
  - Joseph Chouinard in suit and tie, 1951 June, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 172)
  - University of Connecticut Library, 1951 July, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Storrs (Conn.) (Box 1, Image 173)
  - Joseph Chouinard in suit and tie standing in front of a tree, 1951 April, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Unknown location (Box 1, Image 174)
  - Choral conductor Lorna Cooke deVaron with one of her daughters at Tanglewood Music Center, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Chouinard, Joseph Location: Stockbridge (Mass.) Venue: Tanglewood Music Center (Box 1, Image 175)
  - Members of the choral program at Tanglewood in 1953, with conductor Hugh Ross seated in front center, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Chouinard, Joseph Location: Stockbridge (Mass.) Venue: Tanglewood Music Center (Box 1, Image 176)
  - Members of the choral program at Tanglewood in 1953, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Chouinard, Joseph Location: Stockbridge (Mass.) Venue: Tanglewood Music Center (Box 1, Image 177)
  - Members of the choral program at Tanglewood in 1953, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Chouinard, Joseph Location: Stockbridge (Mass.) Venue: Tanglewood Music Center (Box 1, Image 178)
  - Elizabeth Bradley, adoptive mother of Joseph Chouinard, outside a restaurant in Fort Lauderdale, 1955 March, 1 black and white photograph; Photographer: Unidentified Location: Fort Lauderdale (Fla.) On verso: This was taken after we had dinner in this lovely place in Fort Lauderdale the day we went on The Cruise beautiful. (Box 1, Image 179)